Shane Davis

IT Analyst

928-607-3019, ShaneDavisABQ@gmail.com

Executive Summary

Shane has several years of experience in the Information Technology Industry and has created and managed a variety of projects such as software/hardware installation and distribution.

Shane also has several years of experience in customer and IT support in the Health Care Industry. Shane has maintained/serviced hardware (PCs/Tablets/Desktops) and software while using the ServiceNow ticket management system.

Shane is a well-organized, analytical individual who excels at working with detail. He works well remotely using modern teleconferencing technologies and also enjoys working in teams. Shane also has extensive experience working with diverse customer issues and needs. Shane has had several years working with customer conflict management.

- Software Skills MS Office/365, HTML, CSS, Adobe Photoshop,
 Adobe Acrobat, Adobe InDesign, Javascript, Bootstrap, Sharepoint,
 Service Now, Skype, ColdFusion, php.
- **Communication/Customer Skills -** customer relations/conflict management, consumer retail, IT hardware, and software support.

Work History

June 2015 - April 2019

Kemtah - Unity BPO

Shene provided Remote Desktop Support nationally for homehealth/hospice nurses and doctors. Performed asset/inventory management using remote networking tools while providing client voice/email technical support.

- Microsoft Office, SharePoint
- ServiceNow Ticket Management System
- Documented instructions and guides for resolving common IT issues for new employees
- Provided Remote Support
- Gained familiarity with medical professionals

December 2014 – September 2015

Affordable Solar Group, LLC

Shane worked as a Desktop Assistant for Affordable Solar Group, with a team to support three different companies. Support was provided both to local companies and overseas (Puerto Rico).

- Microsoft Office
- Deployed software across networks, and worked with a team to discern the most expedient method for proliferating software over the network while minimizing the negative impact to end-users
- Performed physical maintenance on computers, including cleaning and upgrading
- Have experience in ticket-based troubleshooting systems and problem resolution both in-person and remotely
- Worked through both email and Remote Login customer service experience across multiple fields

October 2008 – November 2014

Albertsons, LLC

Shane worked for several years in a retail position as a Courtesy Clerk he helped facilitate positive customer relations, worked to maintain the store's physical appearance, and handled money as a cashier to assist during high traffic hours.

- Responsible for both client and management facing duties
- Worked with a diverse range of customers and employed successful conflict resolution techniques as problems arose
- Commonly volunteered to take extra shifts for co-workers and worked overtime

.

Education

Current Training

Shane is continuing to train in php, JavaScript, ColdFusion and seeking further training in the MURA Content Management System.

Technical Training School

Shane attended Westmec's IT Security program to further his expertise in the computer support field.

High School

Shane graduated from Flagstaff Arts and Leadership Academy in 2004.